question_data = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The name of the main character of the video game &quot;The Legend of Zelda&quot;, is Zelda.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},

                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "English new wave musician Gary Numan founded the video game development company Facepunch Studios in March 2009.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Luigi is taller than Mario?", "correct_answer": "True",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Pac-Man was invented by the designer Toru Iwatani while he was eating pizza.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "The ultimate phrase used by Pharah from Overwatch is: &quot;Justice rains from above!&quot;",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Rebecca Chambers does not appear in any Resident Evil except for the original Resident Evil and the Gamecube remake.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "In Splatoon, the Squid Sisters are named Tako and Yaki.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "The end credits sequence in Grand Theft Auto 5 is over half an hour long.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "In the game Dead by Daylight, the killer Michael Myers is refered to as &quot;The Shape&quot;.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "In &quot;Undertale&quot;, the main character of the game is Sans.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "In Pok&eacute;mon, Arbok evolves into Seviper.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "In &quot;Need for Speed: Porsche Unleashed&quot;, the player can only drive cars manufactured by Porsche.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
